Soil, Seed & Water is introducing our garden bed. An 8 by 4
foot design with steel corner
posts and room to grow.
So the same garden beds that are on our giveaways are also
going to be added to our inventory.
Not only that, but we have also put together a beautiful demo
video so that you know
exactly how you need to put it together.
This design uses 4 steel posts and 12 boards. 6 long and 6
short, stacked in 3 courses.
With a second person, slide the boards into the corner slots.
Keep the frame square
and secure it with the specified hardware before filling.
Start the filling sequence with pea gravel at the bottom for
drainage. Follow your site
and planting plan for the amount.
Place soil cloth on top of the pea gravel and fit it into the
corners. This helps
keep fine soil particles from clogging the pea gravel drainage
layer.
Above the cloth, add a layer of clean raw wood chips. This is
inside the bed, below
the rich potting soil.
Add rich potting soil above the wood chips. Top it off with
Nature's Blanket, our
dark, chocolate brown mulch, enhanced with compost and worm
castings. From bottom to
top, pea gravel, soil cloth, clean raw wood chips, rich potting
soil and Nature's Blanket.
So we have the garden beds for $599 for a limited
time only. So please, go in if
you want these beds, hit us up, let us know.
For a limited time, get your garden bed kit for just $599.
It includes 4 steel
posts, lumber, pea gravel and soil cloth.
Delivery, soil, mulch and amendments are sold separately. Now
taking orders at Organic
Soil Wholesale. Choose your quantity online. No payment
required today.